Welcome back, and let's take a look at the correct code statements
Selamat berjumpa lagi, mari kita lihat statemen kode yang benar yang
needed to implement each of these comments.
yang dibutuhkan untuk mengimplementasikan tiap komentar.
So for this first comment here, asking us to create a new ArrayList object
Untuk komentar pertama ini, meminta kita membuat objek ArrayList baru,
called restaurantsToTry, and containing a list of strings.
bernama restaurantsToTry, dan berisi list string.
The code for that looks like this.
Kode tampak seperti ini.
So we have ArrayList of type String,
Jadi ada ArrayList dengan tipe String,
the object name restaurantsToTry = new ArrayList of type String.
nama objek restaurantsToTry = ArrayList baru tipe String.
And note that when instantiating an ArrayList,
Perhatikan bahwa saat mengawali ArrayList,
we don't need to input any parameters here.
kita tidak perlu memasukkan parameter di sini.
Now for this second comment, asking us to add a restaurant called
Selanjutnya, komentar kedua meminta kita untuk menambahkan sebuah restoran bernama
Morning Cafe to the ArrayList, the code looks like this.
Morning Café ke dalam ArrayList, kodenya tampak seperti ini.
So we have restaurantsToTry.add and it's taking in Morning Cafe as its input.
Jadi ada restaurantsToTry.add dan mengambil Morning Café sebagai inputnya.
So here's what that looks like visually.
Beginilah tampilannya secara visual.
So using our .add method,
Dengan memakai metode .add,
we've added Morning Cafe at the zeroth index of our restaurantsToTry ArrayList.
kita menambahkan Morning Café di indeks ke-nol pada ArrayList restaurantsToTry.
So now onto the third comment,
Sekarang kita ke komentar ketiga,
asking us to add another restaurant called BBQ Time.
yang meminta kita menambahkan restoran lain bernama BBQ Time.
So the code looks really similar.
Kodenya tampak sangat mirip.
We have restaurantsToTry.add, and
Ada restaurantToTry.add, dan
this time, it's taking in BBQ Time as its input parameter.
kali ini, mengambil BBQ Time sebagai parameter inputnya.
So here's the code again, and this time,
Inilah kodenya, dan kali ini,
we're adding in BBQ Time as the first index of this ArrayList.
kita tambahkan BBQ Time sebagai indeks pertama ArrayList ini.
So now onto our fourth comment.
Sekarang ke komentar keempat.
So the user has just tried our Morning Cafe restaurant.
Pengguna baru saja mencoba restoran Morning Café.
So we want to go ahead and remove it from our ArrayList.
Jadi, kita ingin lanjut dan membuangnya dari ArrayList kita.
So all we need to do is use the restaurantsToTry.remove method, and
Yang perlu kita lakukan adalah menggunakan metode restraurantsToTry.remove, dan
then take in Morning Cafe as its parameter.
kemudian memasukkan Morning Café sebagai parameternya.
So for our fourth comment, the user has just tried our Morning Cafe restaurant,
Jadi, untuk komentar keempat, pengguna baru saja mencoba restoran Morning Café.
and so we just want to remove it from the restaurant's ArrayList now.
Maka kita hanya ingin membuangnya dari ArrayList restoran saat ini.
So the code for that looks like this, restaurantsToTry.remove, and
Kodenya akan tampak seperti ini, restraurantsToTry.remove, dan
it takes in Morning Cafe as its input parameter.
ini mengambil Morning Café sebagai parameter inputnya.
So visually, using the .remove method, we remove Morning Cafe and that shrinks
Secara visual, menggunakan metode .remove, kita membuang Morning Café dan ini meringkas
the size of the array and moves BBQ Time up to the zeroth index of the ArrayList.
ukuran array dan memindahkan BBQ Time ke indeks ke-nol pada ArrayList.
So onto our last comment.
Menuju komentar terakhir.
So we want to get the length of the list and
Kita ingin mengambil panjang list dan
then store it in an integer called numberOfRestaurants.
menyimpannya sebagai integer bernama numberOfRestaurants.
So the code for that looks like this.
Kode untuk itu tampak seperti ini.
We have int numberOfRestaurants = restaurantsToTry.size.
Kita punya numberOfRestaurants #NAME?
Remember for ArrayList, when we use the method size, it doesn't take in any
Ingatlah bahwa untuk ArrayList, saat kita menggunakan metode size, tidak akan
input parameters and it retrieves for us the number of elements in the list.
mengambil parameter input apa pun dan mengambil jumlah elemen dalam list.
So in our case right now, the size of the ArrayList is just one.
Dalam kasus kita saat ini, ukuran ArrayList hanya satu.
[BLANK_AUDIO].
[BLANK_AUDIO].